instoremag.com 2015-02-23

# Privacy Policy « SmartWork Media SmartWork Media

* * *

_Updated MARCH 1, 2013_

The following statement details the manner in which SmartWork Media treats the information you provide while using [www.instoremag.com](http://instoremag.com/index.php),[ www.smartjewelryshow.com](http://smartjewelryshow.com/), [www.smartworkmedia.com](http://smartworkmedia.com/), [www.invisionmag.com](http://invisionmag.com/) or any other SmartWork Media™ site.

Please read this Privacy Statement carefully. Your use of, accessing, and/or registration on any aspect of our sites will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree to these terms, you should not use our services and sites. If you have any questions regarding our privacy statement, contact us by e-mail at [ privacy@smartworkmedia.com](mailto:privacy@smartworkmedia.com).

This Privacy Statement may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page, so check back often. Any change, update or modification we make will be effective immediately upon posting on our site(s). If we plan to start using the information collected from our users in a way that is substantially different from that stated at the time of collection, we will send those users written notice of the change by email. Your continued use of our sites and services at that point will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Statement.

## Collection of Personal Information

For the most part, you may visit our sites without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information.

As you browse our sites, we collect log file, IP address of your computer, and other standard tracking data we use to evaluate site traffic and usage patterns. Such information is aggregated with tracking data from all site visitors. That information is typically used to adapt our sites according to your preferences.

In addition to this, portions of our sites may require you to give us personally identifiable information, such as your name, job title, company, physical mailing address, e-mail address, telephone and fax numbers for:

(i) subscriptions to our publications, including e-newsletters;  
(ii) registration to attend SmartWork Media trade shows, conferences and events;

If you choose to provide us personal information, its main use is to deliver the service you requested. However, it may be used in other manners as follows in the paragraph below.

## Sharing of Personal Information

We may share your personal information with our affiliates and with our partners, including our exhibitors, sponsors and advertisers, for marketing, advertising, and/or product/service offering purposes. Also, we do occasionally rent e-mail lists compiled from e-mail addresses gathered from our sites. While we will make our best efforts to ensure all such third parties follow appropriate privacy policies and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided, SmartWork Media does not bear any responsibility for their actions or policies.

If you do not wish to have your personally identifying information shared, or if you do not wish to receive future commercial communications from us by e-mail, you may unsubscribe or opt-out, as described below – see “Opt-Out Option.”

## Removing or Correcting Your Information

If you would like to update, remove or correct your information and are unable to do so through your user profile, please contact [ privacy@smartworkmedia.com](mailto:privacy@smartworkmedia.com).

## Links and Third-Party Websites

Typically, our website(s) contains external links to other websites — mostly those of advertisers. We have no control over, and are not responsible for information gathered by these other websites. Do not construe our linking to these website as endorsement of these websites or the products or services associated with such websites. Users of our sites should also be aware that, when you voluntarily disclose personal information in comments areas or bulletin boards, that information may be collected by others and might possibly result in unsolicited messages from others.

## Opting Out

On registration pages for print magazine subscriptions, bulletins, and trade show registration, you can manage what communications you receive by stating preferences regarding advertising and promotional communications from SmartWork Media or our partners. Should visitors accept promotional email from SmartWork Media, any email they receive will include instructions on how to be removed from our promotional email list.

If you do not wish to have your personally identifying information shared, or if you do not wish to receive future commercial communications from us by e-mail, you may change your preferences at any time simply by: (i) writing to us (and please include your e-mail address), or (ii) by following the unsubscribe instructions contained within the e-mail you receive from us. We will update your preferences as soon as possible. If you have registered on any part of our sites, please go to that area of the site to change or update your profile, preferences or information to keep all such data accurate and up-to-date.

Please note that if you opt-out as described above, we will not be able to remove your personal information from the databases of third parties with which we have already shared your personal information (meaning, those to whom we have provided your personal information prior to our receipt of your opt-out request).

To opt out of future communications from any such third parties, please contact the third party sender directly. SmartWork Media does not bear any responsibility for ensuring that any third party complies with your opt-out or unsubscribe request for its own lists.

## Questions About Our Policy

If you have any questions regarding our privacy statement, you are welcome to contact us by letter at the address below, or by e-mail at [ privacy@smartworkmedia.com](mailto:privacy@smartworkmedia.com). We read every message submitted and try to reply promptly to every one.

SmartWork Media  
12 W 37th St, Ste 502  
New York, NY 10018
